迈克:停这,我们要爆炸了!
Mike: Stop there, we're gonna crash!
凯特:等等,等等,别动.
Kate: Wait, wait, just don't move.
迈克:好,行,谢谢.
Mike: OK, alright, thank you.
凯特:你知道,迈克,我今晚玩的很开心.
Kate: You know, Mike, I had great time tonight.
迈克:哦,我也是,凯特.
Mike: Oh, I did too, Kate.
凯特:而且昨晚我也很开心.
Kate: And I had a great time last night.
迈克:哦,我也是,凯特.
Mike: Oh, me too, Kate.
凯特:你知道,也许我们应该重新开始约会.
Kate: You know, maybe we should start dating again.
迈克:凯特,不知道我们什么时候有时间.反正每晚都和你在一起.
Mike: Kate, I don't know when we'd have the time.I spend every night with you.
凯特:我知道,那是我的意思.也许我们应该约会,约会.
Kate: I know, that's what I mean.Maybe we should be dating dating.
迈克:哦,明白了,
Mike: Oh, I get it, I get it.
明白了.你是要我进你屋不用敲门.
You want me to come to the door instead of honking.
凯特:不.那么,
Kate: No.Well, yes actually.
就这样吧.
But it would be nice if we were officially seeing each other,
但是如果我们正式地看待对方,那很好;而且我知道承担责任的想法使你害怕……
and I know that the idea of commitment frightens you...
迈克:哇……什么味?什么东西烧着了.
Mike: Wow...smell that?Something's burning.
凯特:为什么我提及约会的话题,你就想逃呢?
Kate: Why do you always run when I bring up the subject of dating?
迈克:凯特,听着,我没有……啊!
Mike: Kate, look, I don't....Aarrghh!
凯特:啊!
Kate: Arrgghh!
迈克:小心!哦.
Mike: Look out!Oh.
埃迪:你们吓到我了.
Eddy: You guys scared the heck out of me.
迈克:哦,行了,埃迪,这是我的房间.
Mike: Oh, come on Eddy, this is my apartment.
埃迪:行,道歉接受了.
Eddy: Alright, apology accepted.
迈克:行了,埃迪,行了,出去!
Mike: Come on, Eddy, come on, get out!
埃迪:不,不,迈克,我有真正重要的事告诉你.
Eddy: No, no, Mike, I got something real important to tell you.
凯特:埃迪,迈克,而且我也有很重要的事要说.
Kate: Eddy, Mike and I are talking about something important too.
迈克:呀,埃迪,
Mike: Yeah, Eddy, we were talking about...Eddy, how you doing?
我们正在谈论……埃迪,你怎么样?好久不见了.
Long time no see.
埃迪:不,不!我再也憋不住了!
Eddy: No, no!I can't hold this in any longer!
迈克,凯特,
Michael, Kate, I'm getting married.
我要结婚了.是的,一开始我也高兴得说不出话来.
Yeah, I was struck dumb with joy at first too.
凯特:埃迪!
Kate: Eddy!
迈克:你在说什么呀?你要结婚了,呀,不错!
Mike: What are you talking about?You getting married, yeah right!
埃迪:嘿,
Eddy: Hey, I'm serious, Mike.
我是认真的.现在,
Now, I know in the past I may have been a little foot loose...
我知道在过去我是个失足……我想你们甚至说……那是什么词?
I suppose you could even say...what's the word?
迈克:浪子.
Mike: Sleazy.
埃迪:是的.但是我变了个人.
Eddy: Yeah.But I'm a changed man.
而且如果不是因为你和凯特,我就永远不会认识我的爱人蒂娜.
And if it weren't for you and Kate, I never would have met my beloved Tina.
迈克:等……等等.蒂娜!不是那个戴帽子的女孩吧.
Mike: W...wait a minute.Tina!Not Tina the hat check girl.
埃迪:她做很多事情.我们的浪漫史的开始你们看到了,
Eddy: She does so many things.
我们也希望你们看到结局.你是我最好的朋友,
Now you guys were there for the start of our romance and we'd like you
迈克,你愿意做我的伴郎吗?
there for the end.You're my best friend, Michael, will you give me away?
迈克:埃迪,我真不能相信,你真的要结婚了.
Mike: Eddy, I can't believe this, you're actually getting married!
嗨,听着,
Hey, look, look, before you do anything just go downstairs and spend ten
听着,在你行动以前,先到楼下跟我的父母呆上十分钟.
minutes with my parents.
凯特:迈克!行了,这是一个好消息.这不是什么可以开玩笑的事情.
Kate: Mike!Come on, this is wonderful news.It's not something to joke about.
婚姻是件美妙严肃的事,对吗,埃迪?
Marriage is a very beautiful and serious thing, right Eddie?
蒂娜:唷,唷,埃迪!等你看看我的嫁妆.
Tina: Yoo hoo, Eddie!Wait till you see my trousseaux.
埃迪:没有什么事情比这要紧的了.
Eddy: It doesn't get any more serious than this.
本:现在,跳起争球……呀!
Ben: And now, for the tip off...Yeah!Seaver scores again!
西维尔再次得分!我得找些朋友.
I gotta get me some friends.
埃迪:让道,小滑头.
Eddy: Get out of the way, squid lips!
本:这车真酷.
Ben: What a cool machine.
埃迪:对,当我上楼跟迈克谈话,你可以闻闻车内装潢.
Eddy: Yeah, well while I'm upstairs talking to Mike,
呀!!!你在干什么呢?
feel free to sniff the upholstery.Ya!!!What are you doing sleeping?
睡觉!快点,我们要去举行婚礼.
Come on, we got a wedding to go to.
迈克:啊!婚礼!行了,现在是早晨.
Mike: Ah!Wedding!Come on, it's morning.
埃迪:对,但是我们要去拉斯维加斯.
Eddy: Yeah, but we have to get to Vegas.
迈克:维加斯!就是,拉斯维加斯!
Mike: Vegas!As in, Las Vegas!
埃迪:就是,婚礼就在那里.
Eddy: Well, that's where the wedding is.
迈克:哦,行了,埃迪,你昨天晚上没有告诉我这些.
Mike: Oh, come on, Eddy, you didn't tell me that last night.
埃迪:作为我的伴郎,你应该知道这些事情.快点.
Eddy: Well as my best man, you're supposed to know these things.Come on.
听着,我们飞往维加斯,
Listen, we'll fly to Vegas, have the wedding, see naughty girls on ice,
举行婚礼,看冰舞.我们周一回来.
we should be back by Monday.
迈克:哦,行了,天哪,这太疯狂了.
Mike: Oh, come on, man, this is crazy.
埃迪:不,不,等你看到溜冰再说.
Eddy: No, no, wait till you see 'em skate.OK, here's the tickets.
好了,这是飞机票.这是戒指……呃……我还忘记了什么?
Here's the rings...errrm...is there anything I'm forgetting?
迈克:堰血.
Mike: Blood tests.
埃迪:哪!我不需要.
Eddy: Na!I don't need 'em.
我可以娶个黑猩猩,也没人可以过问;那就是维加斯的美妙之处.
I could marry a chimpanzee and no-one would care; that's the beauty of Vegas.
迈克:好.
Mike: OK.
本:嗨,埃迪,这些坐位尝起来比闻起来要好.
Ben: Hey Eddy, these seats taste better than they smell!
埃迪:本,别把口水流在车上!
Eddy: Ben, quit slobbering in my car!
还有件事,
One more thing, Mike;
迈克;如果你把这整个结婚的事情保密,我不胜感激.
I'd appreciate it if you'd keep this whole marriage thing a secret.
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
埃迪:我父母不太高兴.我告诉他们,
Eddy: My parents aren't too happy about it.
我和蒂娜订婚了,我妈就从窗口飞了下来.
I told them, Tina and I were engaged, my Mom flung herself out of the window.
克莉丝:本说他十分钟后把车开回来.他想让劳拉.
Chrissy: Ben said he'll have the limo back in ten minutes.
林恩闻闻这味道.
He wants Laura-Lynn to sniff the upholstery too.
埃迪:本!本!
Eddy: Ben!Ben!
克莉丝:如果你要我打扫垃圾,
Chrissy: If you want me to clean this dump,
那么你先付给我两块钱.
then I want my two Bucks in advance.
迈克:哦,嗨,你相信我,是吗,妹子?
Mike: Oh, hey, you trust me don't you kiddo?
克莉丝:我是什么,本?
Chrissy: What am I, Ben?
迈克:好.行了,好.两块钱.
Mike: OK.Alright, OK.Two Dollars.
克莉丝:你去哪里?
Chrissy: Where are you going?
迈克:啊……我去……呃……我和埃迪去旅行.
Mike: Ah...I'm going to...err...I'm going on a little trip with Eddie.
克莉丝:这些是谁的戒指,项链?
Chrissy: Whose rings are these?
迈克:啊……这些是我的.
Mike: Ah...those are mine.
克莉丝:你要结婚戒指干嘛?你又没有结婚,是吗?
Chrissy: What are you doing with wedding rings?You're not married, are you?
迈克:啊,听着,进一步考虑之后,我真的不需要你帮忙了,
Mike: Ah look, on second thoughts I really don't need your help, OK?
好吗?行了,出去.(接电话)喂.
Alright, move it out.Let's go.(on the phone) Hello.
是的,凯特,开始准备你的行李,婚礼在维加斯举行.
Yeah, Kate start packing your bags.This wedding is in Vegas.
麦琪:迈克在哪?你知道,
Maggie: Where's Mike?You know I called up the garage about ten minutes ago.
我十分钟前打电话给汽修厂了.你有见到他吗,杰森?
Have you seen him, Jason?
杰森:没有.
Jason: No.
克莉丝:他说他和埃迪一起去旅游.但是他没有和埃迪却,
Chrissy: He said he was going on a trip with Eddie.
他和凯特去的.
But he didn't go with Eddie, he went with Kate.
杰森:他出去和凯特,约会!
Jason: He's out with Kate, on a date!
克莉丝:他带了很多内衣.
Chrissy: He took a whole lot of underwear.
本:迈克和埃迪旅行去了.
Ben: Mike went on a trip with Eddie.
克莉丝:他和凯特一起旅行的.
Chrissy: He went on a trip with Kate.
本:埃迪!
Ben: Eddie!
克莉丝:凯特!!你会相信谁;你读二年级的女儿,
Chrissy: Kate!!Who are you gonna believe;
还是这个笨蛋?
your daughter who's reading at second grade level, or shallow head here?
本:那就是你们想知道的.我说埃迪用高级轿车接迈克去维加斯去结婚.
Ben: That's what you know.
I say Eddie pick Mike up in a limo to take him to Vegas to get
married.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
本:迈克怎么会娶埃迪?
Ben: Why would Mike marry Eddie?
杰森:哇,等一下,我们……别惊慌,这可能是本的另一个愚蠢错误.
Jason: Wow, wait a minute, let's...Don't panic, this might be another one of Ben's
bone-head mistakes
麦琪:豪华轿车,杰森,还有许多内衣.
Maggie: In a limo, Jason, with lots of underwear.
克莉丝:还有结婚戒指.
Chrissy: And wedding rings.
麦琪:哦,杰森,我们该怎么办?
Maggie: Oh, Jason, what are we gonna do?
开萝尔:我想指出的是,没有必要去认为迈克在犯错,
Carol: I'd just like to point out that there's no need to think that Mike's
因为你们的婚姻也是这样的.
making a mistake just because your marriage's turned out the way it has.
杰森:你知道,麦琪,她说的对.
Jason: You know Maggie, she's right.
迈克:各位,抱歉,
Mike: Excuse me everybody, can I have your attention please!
请注意听我说!我的好朋友,埃迪和蒂娜要结婚了,
My good friends, Eddie and Tina here are getting married,
我们去拉斯维加斯,因此我希望你们和我一起祝他们好运.
when we get to Las Vegas,
好吗?饮料我买单.
so I hope you'll join me in wishing them the best of luck.OK?
乘客:喔!蒂娜:而且我想让所有人认识…… 我相让世界认识,我的伴娘!
The drinks are on me.Passengers: Woo!!Tina: And I want you all to meet...
朱莉,是吗?
heck I want the world to meet, my maid of honour!It's Julie, isn't it?
凯特:不,凯特.
Kate: No, it's Kate.
蒂娜:好,和这个好男人,
Tina: OK, and the best man, my Mikey,
我的迈克,我碰到意中人的时候正和他在一起,
who I was going out with when I met my honey man,
而他又和我背后的伴娘在约会,
who was going out with my maid of honour behind my back,
那时候我还没意识到,在她把名字变成朱蒂前.
before I had a back, before she changed her name to Julie.
乘客:什么?你们在说什么呢?
Passenger: What?What are you talking about?
埃迪:对不起,小甜心.
Eddy: Excuse me sweetheart.
迈克:嗨!嗨,你去哪里?
Mike: Hey!Hey, where are you going?
埃迪:哦,去帮帮这些可怜的加班的年轻女人.
Eddy: Oh, to give these poor over-worked young ladies a hand.
迈克:哦,嗨,
Mike: Oh, hey, I just wanted to say,
我只是想说,对不起我不能为你举办单身汉告别晚会.
I'm sorry I can't throw you a bachelors party.
埃迪:唉,没关系,你可以在我结婚后再开.
Eddy: Man, that's OK; you can do it after I'm married.
迈克:不,真的.我能做的不只是为每个人买些饮料.
Mike: No, really, it's the least I could do buying all these drinks for
我是说,嗨,我的兄弟能结几次婚?
everybody.I mean, hey, how many times is my bro gonna get married?
埃迪:谁知道?
Eddy: Who knows?
迈克:啊……行了,埃迪,你什么意思?你爱蒂娜,对吗?
Mike: Ah...come on Eddie, what do you mean?You love Tina, right?
埃迪:啊……为什么不爱呢?
Eddy: Ah...what's not to love?
迈克:对呀,那么……那么你们一定会相处的很好!
Mike: Yeah, so...so you guys really get along!
埃迪:哦,她没有对于期望什么,迈克,但是我可以给予.
Eddy: Oh, she expects nothing from me, Mike, and I can deliver.
迈克:那不错,埃迪.
Mike: That's good, Eddy.
埃迪:你知道,我告诉你一些事情;我没有真的打算安定下来直到……那不实际.
Eddy: You know, I'll tell you something;
但是,
I didn't really plan on settling down till...well never actually.
嗨,婚姻会是儿戏.
But hey, what the heck, marriage'll be a hoot.
迈克:儿戏!
Mike: A hoot!
埃迪:对.我之前从来没遇到像蒂娜这样的女人……也许除了格洛里亚.
Eddy: Yeah.I have never ever met a woman like Tina before...
我应该打电话给格洛里亚.
except maybe Gloria.I have to call Gloria!
迈克:喔喔,埃迪,埃迪,谁是格洛里亚?
Mike: Wow wow, Eddie, Eddie, who's Gloria?
埃迪:我应该今天晚上和这个妞出去的,
Eddy: This girl I was supposed to go out with tonight,
要是没有出现这个婚礼.
until this whole wedding thing came up.
迈克:埃迪!埃迪,行了,伙计!你就要结婚了.
Mike: Eddy!Eddy, come on, man!You are getting married.
埃迪:那,还没到明天呢.
Eddy: Well, not till tomorrow.
乘客:那是因为我结过婚了,是吗?瞧瞧我结婚戒指……没了.
Passenger: It's because I'm married, isn't it?See my wedding ring...gone.
迈克:啊,凯特……凯特,听着,我要跟你谈谈.
Mike: Ah, Kate...Kate, look, I need to talk to you.
乘客:谈些什么?
Passenger: What about?
迈克:私下谈.
Mike: In private.
乘客:哦.
Passenger: Oh.
迈克:不,行了.
Mike: No, come on.
乘客:谢谢你的饮料,迈克……朱莉.
Passenger: Thanks for the drinks, Mike...Julie.
迈克:听着,听着,凯特……
Mike: Look, look, Kate...
凯特:在洗手间!什么事情呀?
Kate: In the bathroom!What is going on?
迈克:我已经想了,这整个婚姻……我不知道,
Mike: I've been thinking, this whole marriage business...
这只是,
I don't know, it's just it's really made me think.
这真的让我去思考.那么你怎么知道你准备好结婚呢?
And how do you know when you're ready to be married?
凯特:迈克,你是……这是?你在求婚?
Kate: Mike, are you...is this?Are you proposing?
迈克:哦,不,不,不.
Mike: Oh, no, no, no.I'm talking about Eddy!
我是在说埃迪!听着,我认为他在这个婚礼问题上真的犯了大错.
See, I think that he's really making a big mistake with this wedding.
凯特:哦!
Kate: Oh!
迈克:是的.他说了关于婚姻的许多荒谬的话.
Mike: Yes.He's saying all these ridiculous things about marriage.
我是说,他认为婚姻是儿戏.
I mean, he thinks it's gonna be a hoot.
凯特:哦,
Kate: Oh, that's just like you;
这和你一样;认为婚姻是一切美好事物的终点,
to think that marriage is the end of everything good,
而不是开端.
instead of the beginning.
迈克:凯特:行了,我们能不能就谈这个话题?
Mike: Kate, come on, can we stick to the subject please?
凯特:如果埃迪犯错了,至少他准备犯错,而不是害怕犯错.
Kate: If Eddy's making a mistake, at least he's ready to make a mistake instead
of being afraid to commit to a relationship
迈克:害怕!害怕!你说我是害怕!凯特.那……发!那……发!凯特……
Mike: Afraid!Afraid!You calling me afraid!Well...fa!Well, fa!Kate...
老夫人:我认识我第一任丈夫是那方式……在飞机上.
Old lady: I met my first husband that way...on a bi-plane.
蒂娜:哦,我吃了你最后的花生,小甜心.
Tina: Oh, I took your last nuts, shnukums.
埃迪:好,好,我再拿点可爱的蛋糕.
Eddy: Well, well, I'll get more cuddle cakes.
迈克:啊,听着,我去帮埃迪拿点花生.
Mike: Ah, look, I'm gonna go help Eddy get some nuts.
蒂娜:只要想想,在几个小时后,所有这一切就是埃迪的了.
Tina: Just think, in a few hours all this will be Eddy's.
凯特:蒂娜,什么原因让你决定嫁给埃迪的?
Kate: Tina, what made you decide to marry Eddy?
蒂娜:他向我求婚的.
Tina: He asked me.
凯特:就因为这个.
Kate: That's it!
蒂娜:别犯傻了.我有其他原因;重要的原因,例如他的头发.
Tina: Don't be silly.I had other reasons; serious reasons, like his hair.
凯特:你嫁给埃迪因为你喜欢他的头发!
Kate: You're marrying Eddy because you like his hair!
蒂娜:我嫁给他因为他有头发.以前跟我约会的男人,
Tina: I'm marrying Eddy because he has hair.
大多数已经又老又胖又秃.
See most of the guys I've dated have been old and over-weight and bald.
凯特:为什么?
Kate: Why?
蒂娜:从生命趋势图上看,
Tina: From life expectancy charts, it seemed like the way to go.
这是自然规律.埃迪是真正不戴假发的第一个男人.
Eddy's really the first guy who doesn't wear a tupee.
至少我不认为那是假发.
At least I don't think it's a tupee.
凯特:是的,我不认为是假发.
Kate: No, me neither.
蒂娜:想想看,很快我就是爱德华夫人……爱德华夫人……
Tina: Just think, soon I'll be Mrs.Edward...Mrs.Edward...
凯特:泽弗
Kate: Zeff.
蒂娜:那是他的姓?
Tina: Is that his last name?
凯特:蒂娜,我有种感觉,你根本不了解埃迪.
Kate: Tina, I get the feeling you don't know Eddy all that well.
蒂娜:我不想破坏美好时光.
Tina: I don't wanna spoil the fun.
凯特:婚姻是严肃的一步.
Kate: Marriage is a serious step.
蒂娜:哦,这我知道.我妈妈总对我说,
Tina: Oh, I know it is.Mom always told me to look for Mr.
要找个正派先生,他说你一旦找到他,
Right, she said when you find him you get this feeling in your stomach
有种感觉就会从你胃里升起来,而且你知道.那就是那种他见到我爸爸那种感觉.
and you know.That's how it happened when she met my dad.
凯特:哦,那很甜蜜;你爸爸是正派先生.
Kate: Oh, that's sweet; your dad was Mr.Right!
蒂娜:不,也许她当时脑袋进了虫子还是什么……到了她已经嫁给他的时候,
Tina: No, it turned out she had a bug or something...
她的生活就进入了地狱.
by that time she'd already married him, and her life was hell.
凯特:你这家伙,这样的例子值得你去仔细考虑.
Kate: Boy, a story like that really makes you think.
我是说,你不应该犯下大错.
I mean, you don't wanna make a big mistake.
蒂娜:听着,我不知道你怎么从这个事情得到这话的.
Tina: See, I don't know how you get that out of it.
凯特:那还有什么其他意思?
Kate: Well what else could it mean?
蒂娜:为什么等你胃里的感觉,
Tina: Well why wait around for a feeling in your stomach,
当它可以变成气体出去的时候.
when it could turn out to be gas.
迈克:嗨,我想问你.
Mike: Hey, I wanted to ask you.
你已经想好了婚姻会是个什么样子?
Have you really thought about what marriage is gonna be like?
埃迪:哦,我一直在想这个问题.
Eddy: Oh, I can't stop thinking about it.
迈克:你没有任何疑虑?
Mike: You don't have any doubts?
埃迪:你认为我应该有疑虑?你认为这是个机会,
Eddy: You think I should have doubts?
我可能没有做对事情.
You think there's a chance I might not be doing the right thing.
迈克:嗨,那……(凯特在迈克的脑袋里)这和你一样;认为婚姻是一切美好事物的终点,而不是开端…… 嗨,听着,埃迪,如果你幸福,我就幸福.我是百分之一千的支持你.
Mike: Hey, well...(Kate in Mike's head) oh, it' just like you to think that
marriage is the end of everything good, instead of the beginning...
Hey, look Ed, if
you're happy then I'm happy.I'm behind you a thousand percent
埃迪:哦,谢谢,伙计,这对我来说意味着很多.
Eddy: Oh, thanks man, that means a lot to me.
凯特:迈克,我能和你谈谈吗?
Kate: Mike, can I talk to you?
迈克:啊,凯特,凯特,
Mike: Ah, Kate, Kate, yeah, yeah, I was just telling...
是呀,是呀,我在告诉……嗨,
Hey, Kate I just wanted to tell you, I think you were absolutely right.
凯特,我只想告诉你,
You should have seen the look on Eddy's face when I told him this marriage
我想你是绝对正确的.你应该已经看见埃迪脸上的表情了,当我告诉他结婚是个不错的想法的时候.
was a good idea.
凯特:你到底为什么这么做?
Kate: Why on earth would you do that?
迈克:那,因为你告诉我的.
Mike: Well, because you told me to.
凯特:哦,在我跟你说的所有话里,
Kate: Oh, out of all the times I've told you things,
你就挑了这句听.
you pick this one to start listening!
麦琪:是,你好,丘比特教堂吗.
Maggie: Yes, hello, Cubert's Cathedral.
是的,我是想找一对即将犯下大错的一对新人……你说什么,要我自己挑?
Yes, I am trying to find a couple that is about to make a tragic mistake...
那……喂!喂!
What do you mean, take my pick?Well...Hello!Hello!Oh, Jason, it's no use.
杰森,这样没有用的,拉斯维加斯有五十多个教堂.
There must be fifty chapels in Las Vegas.
杰森:嗨,麦琪,马戏团在 上演"淘金者".
Jason: Hey, Maggie, the Gold diggers are headlining at Surfer's Circus.
麦琪:杰森,请努力集中精力.
Maggie: Jason, please try and stay focused here.
杰森:亲爱的,我只想找点让你高兴的事.
Jason: Honey, I'm just trying to find something to be happy about.
这是无意义的.如果我们找到迈克,我们怎么办?
This is pointless.What if we do find Mike, what are we gonna do, ground him?
把他关进他的房间,没有房间服务.
Send him to his suite without room service?
麦琪:我没有放弃.我没有忘记我为什么来这里.
Maggie: I am not giving up.I am not forgetting why I'm here.
杰森:好.行.
Jason: OK.Alright.I'll take the chapels from Adam's Rib to Marriages Awry,
我用心从"亚当肋骨教堂"开始找到"婚姻错误",你从"调皮而美好"找到"勇气".
and you take Naughty but Nice to Zing Zing Zing with my heart.
麦琪:好吧.
Maggie: OK.
蒂娜:有个尼姑是在这结婚的.
Tina: One of The Monkees was married here!
凯特:哦,这真是个好地方.
Kate: Oh, this is quite a place.
埃迪:我们来这是结婚的.
Eddy: We're here to get married.
业主:我们不办集体婚礼.
Owner: We don't do groups.
迈克:不,不,不,先生,我们不结婚.就他们俩.
Mike: No, no, no, sir, we're not getting married.Just they are.
业主:如果借用"一切才刚开始"房间,费用是995元,
Owner: That's nine ninety five for the, "We've only just begun" chapel,
如果借用"你孕育了我孩子",费用是1005元.
or nineteen ninety five for the, "you're having my baby" chapel.
埃迪:那么,有什么不同?
Eddy: Well, what's the difference.
业主:差10元,快点,我给你们带路.
Owner: Ten Dollars.Come on, I'll show you.
迈克:凯特,凯特,我们不能让他们把婚礼进行下去.
Mike: Kate, Kate, we can not let them go through with this.
凯特:我们能干什么呢?
Kate: What are we supposed to do?
迈克:那么,我想是时间当个男子汉了,
Mike: Well, I think it's time to be a man,
然后进去,告诉他们这是个大错误.行,
and to go in there and tell 'em that this is a big mistake.
那么就这么干,告诉他们.
Alright, well go ahead, tell them.
凯特:迈克,这应该出自朋友之口.你告诉埃迪.
Kate: Mike, it should come from a friend.You tell Eddy.
迈克:好.行.
Mike: OK.Alright.I think this wedding is the biggest mistake of your lives!
我认为这场婚礼对于你们是个大错!错误的房间.
Wrong chapel.
主持:嗨,我是米里亚姆.
Officiator: Hi, I'm Miriam, I'm officiating at your wedding.
我将主持你们的婚礼.你们准备好了吗?
Are you kids ready?
埃迪:哦,是的.
Eddy: Oh, yeah.
蒂娜:等等,我还不确定……
Tina: Wait, I'm not sure...
迈克:哦,是的.
Mike: Oh, yes.
蒂娜:好的,我确定.
Tina: OK, I'm sure.
埃迪:你在我就放心了,兄弟.
Eddy: You being here means a lot to me bro.
主持:行,新娘新郎站在这.
Officiator: Alright, the bride and the groom stand here.
伴郎和伴娘站在他们两边.吉伯!!
The best man, and the maid of honour at their sides.Gilbert!!
亲爱的朋友,今天我们大家聚集一堂,来参加这位先生爱德华.
Dearly beloved, we have come here today to join this man,
科尼利厄斯.泽弗和这姑娘蒂娜.
Edward Cornelius Zeff and this woman, Tina Louise, in holy matrimony.
路易丝神圣的婚礼.各位出席为证.
In the presence of these witnesses...
迈克(想):这是他的决定.这是他的生活!
Mike: (in his head) This is his decision.It's his life!
但是我是谁,
And who am I to tell him what to do?
怎么能告诉他该做什么?好像我们的关系也没那么密切.
Like my relationship's working out so hot.
埃迪(想):你是我最好的朋友.你愿意当我的伴郎吗?
Eddy: ( in his head) You're my best friend, Mike.Will you give me away?
凯特(想):应该有人告诉他真相.
Kate: (in his head) Someone should tell him the truth.
迈克(想)你认为我应该有疑虑?你认为这是个机会,
Mike: (in his head) You think I should have doubts,
我可能没有做对事情.
you think I'm not doing the right thing?
凯特(想):这话应该由朋友来说,迈克.你告诉埃迪.
Kate: (in his head) It should come from a friend, Mike.You tell Eddy.
埃迪(想):你在我就放心了,兄弟.
Eddy: ( in his head) You being here means a lot to me, bro.
主持:如果现在有人知道为什么他们不能举行婚礼,现在说……
Officiator: If anybody knows why these two should not be wed, speak now...
迈克:现在!我说,
Mike: Now!I mean, no!Look, you guys, you can't do this.This is not right.
不!听着,
I mean, I don't know...
你们,你们不能这么做.
I just know that marriage is not something you're supposed to fool around
这不对.我是说,
with.I mean, it's more important than that.
我不知道……我只知道婚姻不是可以随便拿来开玩笑.我是说,婚姻比这重要得多.
Marriage is even more important than love,
婚姻甚至比爱情还要重要,因为这关系到两个人要一起度过下半辈子.
because it's about two people spending the rest of their lives together.
这就像两个人就变成一个新人了,如果我不说出来,
It's like two people becoming one new person,
我就不算是朋友.我不知道,
and I wouldn't be a friend if I didn't say something.
也许你认为我不是朋友,因为我说了.
I dunno, maybe you think I'm not a friend because I did.
埃迪:想取消吗?
Eddy: Wanna call it off?
蒂娜:当然,还能怎么样.
Tina: Sure, what the heck.
埃迪:那么,说定了.有人想去看"干一杯酒921"吗?
Eddy: Well, that's settled.Anyone wanna see, Bottoms Up 921?
蒂娜:我想!我想!我就是来就为了说这的,而且我说了.
Tina: I do!I do!I came here to say that, and I said it!
埃迪:嗨,你们一起来吗?好的,我们等会追上你们.
Eddy: Hey, you guys gonna come along?OK, we'll catch up with you later.
主持:那就是为什么我总是先收钱的.
Officiator: That's why we take the money first.
凯特:哇,你刚才做的演讲很不错呀.
Kate: Wow, that was quite a speech you made.
迈克:哦,伙计,那是我,是吗?
Mike: Oh, man, it was me, wasn't it?
凯特:那些东西哪里来的?
Kate: Where did all that come from?
迈克:啊……我不知道.我不知道.
Mike: Ah...I don't know.I don't know.
我刚才一张开嘴,它就出来了.
I just opened my mouth and out it came.
我很想打断自己,但是我又想看看结果.
I would have stopped myself but I wanted to see how it finished.
凯特:但是你相信你所说的……迈克?
Kate: But you did believe what you said...Mike?
迈克:是呀,我刚准备问自己是否相信呢.
Mike: Yeah, I was just gonna see if I believed it.
凯特:我认为你说的很不错.你真让我十分惊讶.
Kate: I thought it was beautiful.You really surprised me.
迈克:是,我也是.
Mike: Yeah, me too.
凯特:那么,你还有什么让我惊讶的吗?
Kate: So, what other surprises have you got for me?
麦琪:哦,杰森,我对这个地方有好感.
Maggie: Oh, Jason, I have a good feeling about this place.
杰森:哇,有一个尼姑就是在这结婚的.
Jason: Wow, one of The Monkees was married here.
麦琪:上帝呀,我们太迟了!
Maggie: My God, we're too late!
迈克:妈妈,爸爸,你们到这里来干什么?
Mike: Mom, Dad, what are you guys doing here?
杰森:麦琪,大度一点.
Jason: Maggie, be big about this.
麦琪:我欢迎你来我们家.我知道我最后会喜欢你的.
Maggie: Welcome to our family.I knew I could get to like you eventually.
凯特:不,不,不.迈克和我没结婚.
Kate: No, no, no.Mike and I aren't married.
蒂娜:迈克,我们的戒指还在你那里?
Tina: Mike, do you still have our rings?
杰森:欢迎来我们家.
Jason: Welcome to our family.
迈克:不,不,不,不,伙计们,我也没跟她结婚.
Mike: No, no, no, no, guys, I'm not married to her either.
蒂娜:埃迪和我需要抵押我们的戒指去看戏.
Tina: Eddy and I need to porn our rings to go to this show.
迈克:好,行.
Mike: Oh, right.
麦琪:迈克,这里发生了什么事情?你没有和任何人结婚?
Maggie: Mike, what's happening here?Aren't you married to anyone?
迈克:不,不,
Mike: No, no, Mom.
妈妈.我来这做埃迪的伴郎,但是他们取消婚礼了.
I came here as Eddy's best man, but they just called the wedding off.
麦琪:这下我可放心了,哦……哦,
Maggie: I am so relieved, oh...
不是说迈克娶你是他所做过的最愚蠢的事情.哦,
Oh, not that marrying you would be the worst thing Mike's ever done.
不,我是说你很有可能是个好姑娘.
Oh, no, I mean there is a chance that you're a fine young lady.
杰森:哦,我有个好主意;在我们说出什么愚蠢的话之前,
Jason: Oh, I got a great idea;
为什么我们不离开这里呢?
why don't we all just leave before we say something stupid?
麦琪:行.
Maggie: Alright.
迈克:啊……凯特,我们重新开始约会,你看怎么样?
Mike: Ah...Kate, what do you say we start dating again?
凯特:那么,我不知道我们什么时候有时间,
Kate: Well, I don't know when we'd have the time,
我们几乎每天晚上见面.
we're seeing each other almost every night.
迈克:哦,我知道了.我知道你会这些的……
主持:他们会回来的.
00:21:59,200
Mike: Oh, I knew it.I knew you'd say that... Officiator: They'll be back.